{
    "subject": "Norman_Mailer",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Maidstone__film_",
    "human_readable": "Norman Mailer produced the film Maidstone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8846625089645386,
            "question": "Who produced the film Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8689157366752625,
            "question": "What is the connection between Norman Mailer and the film Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8503514528274536,
            "question": "Did Norman Mailer create any other films besides Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8213682174682617,
            "question": "Was Norman Mailer involved in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7974116802215576,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Norman Mailer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.682881772518158,
            "question": "What year was the film Maidstone released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6727136373519897,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Norman Mailer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.630608320236206,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any films produced by Norman Mailer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47037628293037415,
            "question": "Is Norman Mailer known for writing or producing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2726331651210785,
            "question": "What type of work is Maidstone?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norman Mailer produced the film Maidstone.",
            "html": "yago_28872_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Norman Mailer known for writing or producing?",
            "html": "yago_28872_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any films produced by Norman Mailer?",
            "html": "yago_28872_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Norman Mailer.",
            "html": "yago_28872_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28872_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Norman Mailer was involved in producing the film \"Maidstone,\" as evidenced by statements about him writing, producing, and directing the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}